# Cj amiel L. Lebios

### Business Development/Customer Support

C.Lebios1998@gmail.com | +63 (985) 1933-109

## **SUMMARY**

I am an experienced professional with a diverse skill set that includes B2B, technical support, outbound sales, SEO, and web development. My track record of success in these areas has equipped me with the ability to deliver results and make a positive impact on any organization. My expertise in building and nurturing relationships with key clients, troubleshooting complex technical issues, driving revenue growth, optimizing websites for search engines, and creating engaging user-friendly websites make me a highly motivated and skilled professional. I look forward to utilizing my skills and knowledge to contribute to your organization's success.

## **SKILLS**

Search Engine Optimization (SEO) • React.js • AngularJS • HTML • CSS • JavaScript • Email • Inbound Marketing • B2B Marketing • 3CX

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **SEO**

Duxstyle Nov 22 - Present

**BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST** 

Callbox Inc. Jul 2021 - Sept 2022

#### **WEB DEVELOPER**

Medprobe Dec 2019 – Jun 2021

#### **CUSTOMER TECHNICAL SUPPORT**

Comcast April 2018 - Dec 2019

#### **EMAIL/CHAT SUPPORT**

Mad Rabbit Co. Nov 2017 - Apr 2018

# **EDUCATION**

**AMA Colleges** | Associate in Computer Technology Graduated yr. 2016 | Butuan City, Agusan Del Norte 8600

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

Inbound Marketing – HubSpot

HubSpot Sales Software - HubSpot

Advanced Search Engine Optimization - HubSpot

Inbound Sales - HubSpot

Frictionless Sales – HubSpot

Academy Coding for Marketers - Sololearn 1165-26346501

Advanced Windows Store App Development Using HTML5 and JavaScript – Coursera